<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
  <title>Jericho's Tavern</title>
  <description>A personal blog about tech, the web, rants and other yap.</description>
  <link>https://djsng.neocities.org/</link>
  <atom:link href="https://djsng.neocities.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 23:53:31 -0300</lastBuildDate>
  <ttl>60</ttl>

<!-- ADD NEW POST HERE -->

  <item>
    <title>The Classic: A Repeat of the Past</title>
    <description>
<![CDATA[<p><small>backported from spacehey blogs</small></p>
<p>First post here, it's a sequel to a rant to another ROBLOX event I've talked about before with my heart.<br></p><p>Update: Added a tiny bit more information following The Games, as I felt I didn't add enough when writing.</p><h1>Sources<br></h1><p>Just want to clear up where my research is from first, because it's best if you look into this yourself before reading my yap and coming to your own conclusions.<br><br></p><ul><li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vfa0w33_T14" target="_self">Chizeled's video is a good place to start.</a>&nbsp;As I'm writing this, it only came out like an hour ago! I used it to double check some research such as with the "pay to win" items, some points, etc. Watch it if you wanna learn more!<br></li><li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=77EdrxzLb2M" target="_self">This greenlegocats video will explain the Live Ops and Boys and Girls Dance Club thing a little better.</a>&nbsp;Yes, it actually happened. Start watching at 10:45 and see for yourself.<br></li><li><a href="https://www.roblox.com/games/17427651911/" target="_self">Play the event yourself too!!!</a>&nbsp;I got most of my game claims from the games themselves, and tried to include screenshots if I remembered.</li></ul><h1>History's Introduction</h1>Okay, so what makes a normal ROBLOX event fun? Well, they should last maybe a month, they should have a good selection of games, and you shouldn't be left confused and lost. The more memorable the event the better, but normally that doesn't make a difference.<br><br>Now, The Hunt: First Edition? It at least made an attempt, but it overwhelmed people with it's 100 games, did easter events in a style people found lazy ("dev hunts"), most of the items ended up being really expensive and event exclusive, and there was very little free prizes among other things. Despite those issues, The Hunt was a return to ROBLOX events and while it had many flaws, some that completely ruined the event, it still had potential and needed some serious feedback to be improved.<br><br>And The Classic?<br>Worse than the last event (subjectively). Hear me out.<br><br><h1>Crunched for Time</h1><br>Let's address the elephant in the room: The Classic just doesn't give you enough time to really grind at your own comfortable pace. It has better compacting sure, and has less games, but the amount of items is still the same! And you'll have to play the same game several times! Not only in a way that's possibly unfair (i.e: completing a whole minigame with crap teammates, super high difficulty etc), but also you only get a week to do it! Why put in effort when there is no effort? That's why I tried it for a few hours, then didn't bother. The grind wasn't even worth it. Lazy of me, sure, but wouldn't that make ROBLOX just as lazy of a company for making this garbage? We gave lots of feedback, did they not listen to all of it?<br><br>I get that the timeframe celebrates history and it's the time between the site's reaction and trademarks being made, but that's only 5 days. Nobody's going to stomach this entire event in five days! At least, I'm not...<p>Let's also add on the fact most people will be busy with school and work and whatnot. So not only is it too short by regular standards, you leave basically no time for anybody who's actually studying right now! If this isn't the shortsighted part of the event...<br>ROBLOX. You are a KIDS game. If the KIDS are busy studying, why would you engineer this event during this time? THINK.<br><br>Not only that, but it also has the same issues as the last event. Most of the good items that were showcased were either pay high amounts to get, or they ended up being extremely tedious to get. Not only that, but there's the same amount of items spread across each game: You can still only get one measly item every few days, and there's still only 5 total. So there's very little to earn without paying, too much to earn by paying. The only real improvement in that area is that they removed the Robux tiers. Even then, they did Tix VERY dirty by making it buy items you can only use in the lobby. The fuck? I don't wanna use a rocket launcher in just one single game, what is this?<br><br>The main prizes aren't even that good. The first item makes no fucking sense to me, the fuck is this? A wrap for my arms? It surely doesn't look like a Tixsplosion reskin. Other than that, I will say that there's accuracy in some of the items, to some degree. There's a buckethead, a helm, and that one hat that gives you wings and a halo. Personally a step up from the ugly and hardly fitting items from last time. Now, that's a huge improvement, but unfortunately still-<br>What? They're making avatar items more expensive AGAIN? Nope, that sounds like modern ROBLOX.<br>Oh, even better, you added back the items you have to pay robux for? And they're still identical to the main items except in gold? Great, what a wonderful event!<br><br>Let's continue to the event itself now.<br><br></p><h1>Inconsistencies, Ahoy!</h1><br>Now, I am not by any means an older player. Depending on who you ask, either I'm older than most of ROBLOX's active playerbase, or I'm not even close to being an 'older' player. But just hear me out.<br>I think ROBLOX is <b>not </b>properly doing the classic theme. Let me explain.<br><br>Since many active people played past 2016, let's start with the things you're more likely to notice:<br>First off, the UI takes modern design hints. The mute music button uses an emoji, and is placed by the modern icons. Now that would be cool in any other game, but this is a classic themed event. You couldn't have hand drawn an icon? What about doing it how old games did and using the text "Mute Music"? At the least, using old color schemes, like 2013+'s blue and grey, or even 2012's red and black?<br>Less noticably, dialogs and chat. While dialog textures the same as they were in 2015 and later on, they still use 2022+ chat bubbles. The opposite also applies to chat, how the chat box is the modern chat box, but they could of used the old chat box, WHICH BY THE WAY, IS STILL SUPPORTED.<br>I can only assume this was likely a corporate decision. I could say a bunch of reasons why this happened, such as corporate greed, or just a dev team who had no idea about ROBLOX's 18 year history... Holy shit, it's going to have been 18 years in September.<br><br>Anyway, there's also safe chat. Of course, they didn't remove chat for people younger than 13... That would be dumb. But they added that little chat bubble from 2008 where you click options and there's buttons... That thing. But they don't have most of the old dialogs, so it feels more like it's there for novelty rather than accuracy. But at least we have old games featured...<br><br><h1>Not Even Classic!</h1><br>Oh sorry, is this event called The Classic? Are we meant to have some old selection, and are we gonna get an event related to oldschool games? Nope, you DON'T. They hyped the event up by listing actually old games like Crossroads and Natural Disaster Survival, but then jinxed it by making nearly none of the games classic. Not to mention, Toilet Tower Defense of all games being in this list is a good example. It can be argued that Adopt Me and Arsenal earned their slots, sure. But Blade Ball? A last event's game, Driving Empire? Dress to Impress? Fucking a dusty road trip? Hell, there's even games here from First Edition! Was it hard to get new games?<br><br>Speaking of, the version of A Dusty Road Trip featured is supposedly, a ripoff. It's a clone of a similar game, just with a bunch of added gamepasses to make some quick bucks. Basically most modern games on the site nowadays. Hell, what if I told you this wasn't the first time? About 2019, they replaced ROBLOX events with this thing called "Live Ops", which you might recognize instead as "This Week on ROBLOX". Did you know the version of Boys and Girls Dance Club featured was stolen? And it wasn't taken down for a good while too, it got featured for a good few weeks! Great management, ROBLOX.<br><br>It probably also doesn't help that this game is also hell to wrap your head around. Just like the first edition, Adopt Me doesn't seem to have a clear cut button for the event. Arsenal, unlike last event, doesn't have one either. Gunfight Arena has a completely unrelated task you have to do before you can even DO the event stuff that gets you what you want. We're suffering! Is that not enough?<br>It's already a lot that most of these games don't follow the old theming, even for new generation games, although that's to be expected at this point. At least Dress to Impress used squared brick textures and tried to make something! The only real relation Bedwars had to old roblox was the penguins held fucking swords and cokes! Is that the best we get as players? Is there no regulation about using old models and trying to use as little modern models as possible?<br><br><img src="https://files.catbox.moe/0mtv1v.png" alt="Modern model among the old road. Game is A Dusty Road Trip."><br><p><br></p><p>Like what the fuck is this? This looks ugly. You have this modern bag model, and it's on an oldschool road, and all of this oldschool text. It looks so out of place. Arguably our avatars are too, but at least there's a toggle.</p><p>Better yet, even the playerbase has some (cheap, although functional) options to fit in with the classic part of this event. Many choose not to, which only beats the dead horse on this event, but there's at least immersion. The player can CHOOSE to come with a classic avatar to feel more immersed. This game doesn't even bother to immerse you.<br><br></p><h1>Rich people, ahoy!</h1><br>Did you not get enough of this event? You wanna blow your money? You like expensive things? 19k Valkrie bundle, go get it. So great, isn't it? Great to get fucked over like this? There's even one for a fedora, named the "Treasure Hunter"... What am I hunting again? I don't feel like I'm hunting, I feel more like I'm doing chores in the house.<br>Great to spend money to get gold variants of a bunch of shit you won't use in the end? Yeah, me too.<br><br>They did this last event too. Make a bunch of gold variants of the items, make it exclusive to either a 800 Robux gold lineup, a 19k bundle that was limited time, or you can pay it for one item out of pocket. This shit was just one fucked up cash grab, and we all got deep in it. Deep ini the chores list, sure.<br><br>But what's the point in the end? Why are we spending so much? Well, because ROBLOX wants to make MONEY! That's the only way I can assume this event was so bad, that the last event was so rushed, that all of the events before it... Just cheap tricks.<br>Because we aren't getting old events anymore. That's obvious.<br><h1>What Else?</h1><br>Other than that though, that's where it ends. I didn't bother to play much in my, what, 3 hours of playing? In Bedwars I got killed by the void, even though the pixels clearly said I died to a penguin. A dusty trip had a vip room, which apparently has a free tshirt to check what's inside! I didn't look yet, I'm too lazy to continue this dogshit event.<br><br>I got into lobbies with lots of noobs on Bedwars and Bee Swarm Simulator. Livetopia has confusing store layouts, and that task is long and tedious. Feels more like a chore. Arsenal was unclear with how you get the quest done, unlike First Edition. Hell, first edition had a whole singleplayer experience! Why didn't we get something like that again?<br><br>That's a... lot to work with. Wow, this event is just as bad as The First Edition.<br>I wrote double than I did my last ROBLOX event rant, and that one was also made with a lot of care.<br><br>Well... I guess that's it.<br>Surely they can't fuck up three times?]]>
    </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 23:53:31 -0300</pubDate>
    <link>https://djsng.neocities.org/posts/2024-05-24-The-Classic-Rant</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://djsng.neocities.org/feed.xml#4</guid>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>WACUP is awesome.</title>
    <description>
<![CDATA[<p><small>Backported from a later March 2023 Blog Archive, has small changes, original blog has a last updated date of March 27th</small></p>
      <p>I was catching up on some SpaceHey just seeing what good stuff there was to read. I sometimes tend to do that, because I like reading dumb shit when I feel like it. In <strike>Athen</strike> Kam fashion, I ended up finding a rant about Winamp. Apparently they got into the Crypto scene, and it looked pretty ugly. Of course, I'm not a big fan of crypto stuff, so I decided "I guess that's another program gone".</p>
      <p>Well, I read through it, couldn't believe the bullshit about Winamp (which as of writing this, I'm uninstalling rn), and I noticed the guy actually linked this replacement called WACUP. It ran on a pretty stable build of WinAmp, added a lot of content, and expanded on it in a better way. I figured I'd give it a shot. If it was shit, well it's better than nothing. If it was good, I'd main it. Well, I downloaded it and decided to see what it was made of.</p>
      <p>God damn, it was fun installing it when I got the time.</p>
      <p>First off, the amount of extra features compared to the build I had previously (and now regret) installing, was kind of amazing. Already at the "check the features you want" phase, I was just trying to process what everything did. It felt way bigger than any other build of WinAmp, and it was almost like a new product. Credits to the WACUP team for all that shit they managed to cram in there, anyway.</p>
      <p>Installed it, and still pretty amazed. I can't tell if they did changes to the setup portion, but if they did they did it alright. Had fun picking out a theme and stuff. Setting everything up was as fun, I was playing with the Discord presence thing for the past 10 minutes, it was fun. Had to manually reinstall the Last.fm scrobbler plugin, but that wasn't too hard.</p>
      <p>I'm playing with it right now. All the themes and plugins they've slammed into this thing is kind of funny. I could mess with this thing for a few hours. But hey, it works exactly for what I needed Winamp and Foobar2000 for: A music player that has Discord Rich Presence and scrobbles to Last FM.</p>]]>
    </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 23:43:39 -0300</pubDate>
    <link>https://djsng.neocities.org/posts/2023-03-14-WACUP-is-Awesome</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://djsng.neocities.org/feed.xml#3</guid>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Technology is Like Magic</title>
    <description>
<![CDATA[<p><small>Backported from March 2023 Blog Archive; extra line + expanded dialog on one line + image added 09/08/24</small></p>
      <p>Windows computers are quite possibly the most confusing and most magical thing to ever exist. No, this doesn't cover windows modifications, or technical depth. Just how I saw it.</p>
      <p>This entry is more so about my own experiences. The good, the bad, and the downright confusing. Now keep in mind, I've used technology since I was maybe 5. So I have both some stories on crazy, awesome things Windows has done, some really broken things that happened, and some confusing things it's done, as well as some bonus stories from my childhood related to technology. Yep, a full length blog again. Let's go.</p>
      <p>Let's start with some good Windows has done. Build some character, to make the smashdown a little more exciting. Well, to start, backwards compatibility is sometimes like good. Like REALLY good, obviously issues but most of the time it's flawless. At the most, I've had issues with certain GameHouse (remember that old game website? Where you used to buy Plants vs Zombies, maybe?) titles, at the worst. Though sometimes the issues aren't as bad, like simply just having some flippy fullscreen on Halo: Combat Evolved. Although there's definitely way worse, like folder detection with some games, but note how compatibility is mostly preserved!</p>
      <p>Other than Compatiblity, there's also, at least in my opinion, how older versions of Windows handled logging in. Windows 8 & 8.1 (2012 & 2014 respectively) and after has a kind of funky user change system, and I'm not a fan of it. Although at Windows 7 (2009), it was pretty smooth, and I really liked how it used to be. </p>
      <img src="https://3.bp.blogspot.com/-XZRO4LXYcp0/T2WPEZLjOQI/AAAAAAAAAT0/aaRRb8skcRo/s1600/Clone+of+Windows+7-2012-03-16-21-51-12.png" alt="Windows 7 login screen" class="small right">
      <p>If you're unfamiliar, or you just never got to experience a computer before, it looked about like this:</p>
      <p>Yeah, there was that nice blue background, and all of the users were displayed in columns. You'd click one, enter your password if you wanted, and you'd be on your way. On Windows 8 and after, you see the first user, and you have to manually switch to another user in the login menu, which I don't like. And my device actually automatically logs into the correct user, which I'm not complaining, cause I don't use the other user on it, lol. Still though, imagine that happening to somebody else's account. Pretty annoying.</p>
      <p>But Windows 7 had this simple design. And it looked pretty nice. Vista (2007)'s was near the same, just with a green and blue gradient instead.</p>
      <img src="https://www.lifewire.com/thmb/MC-zuKZe02q5nfiMimSwqXKYVCI=/1250x0/filters:no_upscale():max_bytes(150000):strip_icc()/windows-xp-safe-mode-login-5a679bd7eb97de001a76647e.PNG" alt="Windows XP login screen" class="small right">
      <p>I cannot for the life of me find a good screenshot, so instead here's one of Windows XP, released around 2001:</p>
      <p>Looks nice, don't it? If only Windows 8 and later was as simple as that. It would have been a nice thing to have, to be able to enjoy a more legacy login screen. Instead we have modern looking junk, and I think everybody knows what the Windows 10 login screen looks like.</p>
      <img src="http://www.wikihow.com/images/1/13/Login-to-Windows-XP-as-the-Administrator-Step-2.jpg" alt="Windows legacy login screen" class="small right">
      <p>There's also a variant for nerds! Here's what that looks like:</p>
      <p>Alright, let's talk about the bad now. I think Performance is a good first thing to put on the table here, because I have a LOOOOOOOOOT to talk about when it comes to performance.</p>
      <p>Firstly, the lack of care. Windows 10 and beyond were designed for SSDs, it's clear it is if you've ever run windows on an HDD, like I am right now, you can just TELL how bad it is. Like you can FEEL how painful it is if you used one before. The constant pausing, the constant crashing of the file explorer, the consistent input lag, etc... You really begin to despite the OS. Even more when your manufacturer thinks it's fucking genius to put an HDD and Windows 10 64-bit together. Yeah.</p>
      <p>Oh, I'm not done. Obviously not. Would you like to talk about the fact that a bug with memory cleaning STILL exists in Windows 11? Yes, I'm fucking serious, In Windows 10, there is a bug where the memory doesn't clean itself. It causes stuttering in games like Assassin's Creed: Origins, Battlefield 1, and it affects both Intel and AMD CPUs. No seriously, there's reddit posts from like 4 years ago (2018 and before) about this shit. It's stupid. </p>
      <p>On top of THAT, it's also a NIGHTMARE to work with other software sometimes. A program I use for controlling CPU/GPU fan speeds and clock literally DOESN'T EVEN WORK. If I reinstall windows without using the "Reset this PC" function, IT CANNOT BE PROPERLY INSTALLED AGAIN. If I try to uninstall it and entirely re-install it, IT CANNOT BE PROPERLY INSTALLED AGAIN. If I completely format my hard drive? You guessed it, CANNOT be properly installed again.</p>
      <p>Like this is a joke. It can't even update without erroring out all the time. Asus has the WORST OEM software I have ever used for a program, and I used to have an HP Laptop. I also used to literally run games that barely met the MINIMUM specs on a Compaq Scenario from 2007. And a 2020 laptop can barely last 5 minutes in the OS. Like???</p>
      <p>Although, the confusing is very short. Sometimes, the OS can magically repair itself. For example, explorer took 10 straight minutes to start after uninstalling a Windows 11 update. Starting the computer the next day, and it's the regular speeds. Sometimes it'd co-operate it, other times it'd randomly lock up random apps whenever it wants. Performance hacks that worked one day, might not another, then suddenly work again the third day. Etcetera, Etcetera, Etcetera.</p>
      <p>Yeah, Windows is kind of a wild one. But why not end it off with a story?</p>
      <p>I used to be pretty crazy of a computer user when I was young. I had once come across this thing, basically a YouTube video of about several shitty bat files you could make and you could call yourself a hacker for knowing how to make them or something. Well, one made about a thousand folders, and named them by numbers. I thought that was funny, so I did it on the desktop, and hid each one in a folder. So you'd go to one folder, you'd see 7, go to another, see 4, go to another, only see 2, etc. My parents didn't like that too much, but I thought it was cool. They were probably mad about it, but it was worth it for the laugh LOL.</p>
      <p>Until next post.</p><br>
      <p>Edit: Would you look at that, Windows forcing 100% of my CPU to be used at all times! I don't remember setting that, I sure wonder what's going on...
More proof Windows does what it wants! Spooky...</p>]]>
    </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 23:42:08 -0300</pubDate>
    <link>https://djsng.neocities.org/posts/2023-03-08-Technology-is-Like-Magic</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://djsng.neocities.org/feed.xml#2</guid>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>A Rant about Stick Aim</title>
    <description>
<![CDATA[<p><small>Backported from March 2023 Blog Archive</small></p>
      <p>Last I checked, I don't think my controller has gyro aim or anything, so this post is exclusively ranting about Stick Aim. Just clarifying.</p>
      <p>Stick aim makes me feel like I'm a god damn caveman. You ever just miss shots for no reason trying to find that enemy? You move too fast or too slow to catch up? It sucks. Yet I prefer movement and crouching on controller compared to keyboard and mouse. So it's like a complete priority shift... Kinda.</p>
      <p>It's like... Good god, isn't there a good in-between? Keyboard and Mouse works, yeah, but theoretically, is there at LEAST a good solution? Something cooler?</p>
      <p>Not really. I get the limitations, and most of the time it's fine, but Stick aim is just so unpolished, because of the lack of precision and it's just... ughhhh.</p>
      <p>Controller gaming just really sucks for shooters.</p>]]>
    </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 23:40:07 -0300</pubDate>
    <link>https://djsng.neocities.org/posts/2023-03-06-Controller-Aim-Rant</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://djsng.neocities.org/feed.xml#1</guid>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>SpaceHey: A Ramble</title>
    <description>
<![CDATA[<p><small>Backported from March 2023 Blog Archive</small></p>
      <p>It's pretty late where I am, and I think I'm about to go to bed. But not before rambling about another thing: SpaceHey.</p>
      <p>I think Spacehey's like the first time I've been really interested in a social media platform. Probably because it's as easy as, say Twitter or Facebook to use. And it's more pleasant to use than both of those combined. After all, it works. It's functional, easy to use, and in my opinion, isn't overwhelming.</p>
      <p>Maybe because I'm a little nerdy. Maybe because the CSS customization strikes a little bit of my fancy. Maybe because it's just so reminiscent of MySpace, I want to see what I could have seen if I was born just 10-20 years earlier.</p>
      <p>Or maybe it's just because we're so used to being confined, confused, and beaten down by shitty, dysfunctional algorithms of modern day, SpaceHey is sort of an escape. An escape from the world of unideal and intrusive technology. Maybe it could be that, is why I use it?</p>
      <p>Honestly, nah. It's just a novelty. The features are cool, but you wanna know the real reason I love using it? <b>Meeting cool people who are like me.</b></p>
      <p>Alright, I'm off to bed. Thanks for listening. See you tomorrow.</p>]]>
    </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 21:42:28 -0300</pubDate>
    <link>https://djsng.neocities.org/posts/2023-03-03-Spacehey-A-Ramble</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://djsng.neocities.org/feed.xml#0</guid>
  </item>

</channel>
</rss>