<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
  <title>Jericho's Tavern</title>
  <description>A personal blog about tech, the web, rants and other yap.</description>
  <link>https://djsng.neocities.org/</link>
  <atom:link href="https://djsng.neocities.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 21:42:28 -0300</lastBuildDate>
  <ttl>60</ttl>

<!-- ADD NEW POST HERE -->

  <item>
    <title>SpaceHey: A Ramble</title>
    <description>
<![CDATA[<p><small>Backported from March 2023 Blog Archive</small></p>
      <p>It's pretty late where I am, and I think I'm about to go to bed. But not before rambling about another thing: SpaceHey.</p>
      <p>I think Spacehey's like the first time I've been really interested in a social media platform. Probably because it's as easy as, say Twitter or Facebook to use. And it's more pleasant to use than both of those combined. After all, it works. It's functional, easy to use, and in my opinion, isn't overwhelming.</p>
      <p>Maybe because I'm a little nerdy. Maybe because the CSS customization strikes a little bit of my fancy. Maybe because it's just so reminiscent of MySpace, I want to see what I could have seen if I was born just 10-20 years earlier.</p>
      <p>Or maybe it's just because we're so used to being confined, confused, and beaten down by shitty, dysfunctional algorithms of modern day, SpaceHey is sort of an escape. An escape from the world of unideal and intrusive technology. Maybe it could be that, is why I use it?</p>
      <p>Honestly, nah. It's just a novelty. The features are cool, but you wanna know the real reason I love using it? <b>Meeting cool people who are like me.</b></p>
      <p>Alright, I'm off to bed. Thanks for listening. See you tomorrow.</p>]]>
    </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 21:42:28 -0300</pubDate>
    <link>https://djsng.neocities.org/posts/2023-03-03-Spacehey-A-Ramble</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://djsng.neocities.org/feed.xml#0</guid>
  </item>

</channel>
</rss>